The reason why I'm here
is that I will protect you
Don't worry, let's go ahead and move on
The moon will always come to the moon
The moon will come to the
moon Let's look at the moon
I used the backside. They're fine.
I hope you're proud of yourself
beating those poor shipwrights.
You're so strong, Zoro.
Whatever.
Might as well go ahead.
Zoro, this way! Got it! No! Over here!
We're leading the way for you, stupid!
But how can you get lost already?
Easy!
Cause I'm rubber!
Alright, good!
Now help me! No prob!
You're gonna pay, you masked bastards!
It's true, we've been undercover
for the last five years.
Ah, but don't worry.
We took our jobs as
shipwrights very seriously.
I understand how shocked you must be.
However, we can't devote any
more time to this matter.
We will achieve our goal
by any means necessary.
So if you're thinking about resisting
for the sake of being difficult,
I suggest you reconsider.
For your own good, as well as ours.
I assume you're already
familiar with Cypherpole.
It's the government's supreme
intelligence agency with eight branches.
Their worldwide bases are
referred to as CP1 through CP8.
Together, they serve as the government's
eyes and ears in every corner of the globe.
Of course I know.
But how do all of you
fit into that picture?
Good question.
As the 9th Cypherpole Unit,
we officially do not exist.
And by virtue of that, we possess a certain
privilege that the other branches lack.
One that necessitates a degree of secrecy.
A privilege?
That's right.
Consider it a blade we wield
in the name of justice.
If a citizen is uncooperative
towards the government,
we may execute them.
You fools you can't use justice
as an excuse for murder.
Recently the government has been
forced to change its way of thinking.
For example, rather than
fearing Pluton's revival,
they have decided to awaken it
to use the ancient weapon as a
force of justice that can bring
an end to the great pirate era.
And now, for some reason, you
want to stand in their way.
It's almost as if you You
have no sympathy for all
of the people constantly
being victimized by pirates.
You should reconsider
where your loyalties lie.
Don't kid yourself.
If the weapon is restored, the world
is going to fight over its power.
It will only breed more destruction.
Are you saying you don't
trust the government, Mr.
Iceberg?
That would be a shame.
Not at all.
It's human nature that
I don't trust. Luchi.
Show some respect.
Remember, you're not my boss anymore.
Kaku, check his pulse.
Excuse me.
Here's the situation.
A while ago, we came up with a bit
of a hypothesis about the blueprints.
All you have to do is lie there and listen
to our hypothesis without saying a word.
Even if your mouth won't cooperate,
your pulse will tell us the truth.
Now that we're all comfortable,
let me explain the thought
process leading to our hypothesis.
First of all,
the way that you allowed us to retrieve
the fake blueprints is highly suspicious.
After you decided that the culprits
were related to the government,
you intentionally revealed
the location of the fakes,
presumably in the hopes
of fooling us. However,
what if your assumption was
wrong and the culprit's intention
was to kill you rather than
to retrieve the blueprints?
In that case, the fakes would be useless,
the real blueprints would be lost,
and the will of the original
shipwrights would not be passed on.
Surely you considered that possibility.
I know you're no fool.
And yet, despite creating a decoy,
you've seemingly made no attempt to
pass off the actual blueprints tonight.
That must mean you've already
entrusted them to someone.
We still don't know where they are,
but we can assume that you don't
have them with you anymore.
That's our hypothesis.
Uh-uh.
No squirming.
This is still just a theory.
I admit,
we haven't found any decisive evidence,
and despite the fact that we've kept you
under surveillance for the past five years,
we've never seen you
do anything suspicious.
Assuming you did entrust
the blueprints to someone,
they would have to be an accomplished
shipwright to make any sense out of them.
Now, if we add that to our theory,
things start to get interesting.
For example, let's take a closer look
at the fake blueprints that you left us.
Here at the bottom, you can see the
signatures of three different shipwrights.
Tom, Iceberg, and Kaido Flam, and
the company name, Tom's Workers.
You probably thought
that this detail wouldn't
mean anything to whoever took the bait,
but you had no idea your
enemies were so close.
That was a grave
miscalculation on your part.
If the person who broke
in had been an outsider,
once they found out that the blueprints
had nothing to do with Pluton,
they would probably have thrown them away.
However,
since we've been shipwrights
ourselves for the past five years,
the names of the designers
are very interesting.
There's a visitor, sir, to see you.
Although many people know of
the legendary shipwright Tom,
the details of his actual
company are shrouded in mystery.
It's believed to have
existed on this island,
but there's no roster
or register to be found.
It was no easy task finding out that
you were one of Tom's apprentices.
What few reports we have indicate
that he taught only two shipwrights,
and a government official
verified that one
of them died in an
accident eight years ago.
Real shame.
I know Kaido Flam was a bit of a loose
cannon, but I sure hate to see him go.
It struck a chord, I thought to myself.
Now, where have I heard that name before?
He said he's a friend from years back.
Do you know anyone named Kaido Flam?
It was about four years ago, shortly
after we started our undercover operation.
He was a man who has passed through
Galilaw's gates many times since.
But only once did he ever use that name.
I remember it, clearly. So do I.
Shall I show him in, sir?
No.
Turn him away.
In other words, Tom's second
apprentice, Cutty Flam, is still alive.
And living in this town, no less.
But now he goes by
Frank what's with
all the secrecy
something going on hey
what are these blueprints for that old
battleship don't call yourself cutty
flam anymore.
It's only a matter of time
before the government targets me.
I want you to take
these and leave this island, Franky.
Seems pretty obvious now, huh?
I can't believe it
took us all these years to
figure out the connection.
Our searches on him turned up nothing.
I must admit that his true
identity was a well-hidden secret.
And because he's an oaf
and a ship dismantler,
we never really gave him much thought.
It's ironic, really.
Since we never questioned our reports,
it didn't occur to us that a dead
person might actually still be alive.
The setup was quite
convenient for you, I imagine.
Since the Franky family often came to
the shipyard to sell lumber,
there were plenty of chances
to pass off the blueprints.
You managed
it well.
He was close when you needed him,
yet always at a safe distance.
That would also explain Why
you were so confident in
dealing with us you knew
that we were looking for the
blueprints in the wrong
place and while it might seem
strange that your most
trusted foreman had not heard
of the blueprints they
couldn't possibly be as close
to you as tom's other
apprentice from this line of
thinking everything checks
out not only that your racing
pulse has confirmed that
our hypothesis this is true.
Come on, hurry! Hey!
You sure this is the right way?
Don't even go there!
Their injuries are pretty bad.
All right, that's gotta be it.
The closed door at the end of the hallway.
Looks like a lot of people
got hurt guarding that door.
Hey!
What are you waiting for?
Cut down the door and beat the bad guys!
We're right behind you!
Hurry it up!
All right, I'll do it, but
not because you told me to!
Hey, Straw Hat, wait!
This is the wrong room, you idiot!
It's the one next door, you hear me?
Don't blame yourself.
You're only human.
And under these circumstances,
no one would be able to hide
the truth from us for very long.
So just be grateful that
justice will prevail in the end.
Thanks so much for the last five years,
but you've outlived your usefulness.
Let's find Franky before the storm hits.
You bastard.
Give process back!
Luffy. Luffy?
You again?
Robin!
I finally found you!
Hey, Luffy!
Where were you when we had to
beat up all those shipwrights?
Robin!
Why did you leave us?
Hold on a sec.
Something's not right here.
Well, well, well.
Paulie.
Straw Hat.
Iceberg.
What is this?
What the hell's going on?
Paulie, damn it, you should have run.
No, what?
This doesn't make sense.
You're making it look like, like you guys
were the ones who were after Iceberg,
but that can't be right.
What the hell are you doing
with those weird costumes on?
Stop screwing with me here!
Hey, Khalifa, Blue Nico, Kaku, Luchi,
say something already, damn it!
Oh yeah, those are the same guys that
were with you back at the shipyard, right?
Right?
Actually, that square-nosed
guy came to our ship. I see.
And the attack on Iceberg
was an inside job.
Wait, what? I don't get it.
Paulie, in all honesty, we're secret
agents working for the world government.
But hey, you'll forgive me
if I say I'm sorry, right?
We were comrades, building ships
together every day from dawn till dusk.
I realize this is quite sudden for you,
so perhaps you'd believe me
if I smashed Iceberg's face.
Just shut the hell up!
I've heard enough.
You were that guy in the
bull mask. Weren't you?
That was the first time
I ever heard your voice.
All those years.
You never said a word.
But you can talk just fine.
I'll teach you to make fun of me!
Holy stop it!
Pipe.
Hitch.
Knife.
Finger pistol.
You still haven't learned
your lesson, have you?
Hey!
Are you okay?
Screw you!
Lucci!
It's pointless to resist.
Our abilities far exceed those of
a normal human, as you can see.
After many years of training, we've
mastered an art called the Six Powers.
These techniques transform
the body into a living
weapon with the strength
of over a hundred men.
Cuckoo!
Stop drinking, Carly!
What about all that debt?
Come on!
I want some cash today!
Next round's on me, okay?
Bring it, Belt! Let's go!
You got it.
Carlyfa, you hussy!
That skirt is way too short!
Hey, give it a rest, Polly.
If you don't like it,
don't look at her, okay?
After all this time, why?
Sorry, Polly.
Our friendship is over.
I have to eliminate you.
Lucci, no, don't!
You jerk!
Leave him alone!
Come go!
I embody... Gotland!
What the?
That didn't work at all.
You're nothing but a pest, Shave.
He's gone!
Finger pistol.
If you weren't made out of rubber,
you'd be dead with a hole in your neck.
Lucky you.
You're protecting him, but why?
Why not?
Because I don't want you to kill him!
You guys were all friends
just the other day.
How could you do this?
We were.
Now, things have changed.
It doesn't matter.
You can say what you want.
You're a bunch of traitors.
The point is, you're my enemy now.
I made a promise with
Polly to beat the crap
out of anybody who tries to hurt Ice Pops.
I see.
You decided to trust him
over us, huh? That's right.
Because you guys took
away one of my friends.
Hey, Robin, what gives?
Why are you acting like this?
If you want to leave the
crew, at least tell me why.
Yeah, and why would you want to team up
with people from the world government?
That's crazy.
Do I have to repeat myself?
I believe I said my farewells to the
cook and the doctor before I left.
Didn't you pass that along, Chopper?
Of course I did, but just because I
heard it doesn't mean I accept it.
How could you do this?
I did it to make my wish come true.
A wish that can't happen
as long as we're together.
And if you can't accept that, I'm sorry.
You may not find it fair, but to accomplish
my goal, I'll make any sacrifice.
I see.
And that includes framing your own
crewmates for attempted murder.
So what is this wish of yours?
I don't have to answer that question.
Are you out of your mind?
Wake up, Robin.
You have no right to do this.
I don't care what it is
you're trying to accomplish.
The consequences are far too great.
I've heard enough.
This is no longer your choice to make
This should shut you up?
No iceberg!
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Nothing you're saying is making any sense!
You expect me to believe this?
Robin, what happened to you?
You're our friend, Rice!
Please, Robin, come back!
Sorry to break up the reunion,
but I'll have to stop you there.
You see, we have a date this evening
with a very important individual,
one that's been over
four years in the making.
We're finished here.
In other words, that means
we're finished with you as well.
Khalifa, how much time is left?
Two minutes.
Here's the deal.
I know this is sudden, but in two minutes,
this building will go
up in a ball of flame.
You're kidding!
Of course not.
Fire is an effective tool for
erasing all sorts of evidence.
If you don't want to be burned alive,
I suggest you leave the
building as soon as possible.
Well, I say that.
But I have no intention of letting you go.
Looks like it's gonna
be us against them and
our friend Robin has
clearly picked her side
Luffy Robin is not one of us anymore.
Do you accept that now?
No, no way.
So noisy anyway, the first
floor is about to set fire!
It won't be pretty!
But to be fair, the
culprits are just pirates.
You can't expect them to be subtle!
You bastards!
That's nice of you to give us
credit for your attempted arson!
But I think that I'll pass!
What's one more crime when we're
going to execute you anyway?
Well,
I suppose I'll take my leave now!
You've done exactly as you were told!
Good work!
Robin!
Don't go!
You're still one of us!
This is farewell.
Robin!
Stop her...
...Straw Hat.
We finally found you!
I won't let you run away again!
Out of my way!
Iron buddy.
How come nothing I do to
these guys even phases them?
In addition to our offensive techniques,
our training has also given us the ability
to make our body as solid as an iron wall.
Of course, your punches
are weak to begin with.
Okay, whatever!
I said out of my way!
Paper of art.
Even though he's big, he sure is fast!
He's moving like his body's made of paper!
Oh no!
Robin!
Move it!
Come on!
Pistol!
Shave.
He disappeared!
My legs are so strong that I can
move faster than your eyes can see.
Moonwalk.
In fact, I can even leap
off of the air itself.
He's flying!
Ten-best... kick!
A slashing attack? Get down! Hurry! Why?
Luffy!
They did all that with a single kick?
No way!
Technically, it was the sharp
gust of wind that followed it.
We call it the Tempest Kick.
We met on your ship, didn't we, Roronoa?
You said you people
aren't real shipwrights.
So does that mean you
lied about the Mary Two?
Unfortunately not.
I was quite honest about my assessment.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Don't go, Robin!
We're not done talking yet!
No, it's over.
This is the last time you'll see me Robin
Movie go after Robin.
Whatever happens.
Don't let her get away
Confident, huh?
You really shouldn't
take your eyes off of me.
Zara!
Finger pistol.
It turns out there are some
things more deadly than bullets
What's your problem?
Get out of my way.
All those punches and
he's not even blinking!
I have him, now go.
Ryan!
Luffy! Sorrel!
I don't believe it how
can they be so strong
I knew you were tough but this is too much
We're not like you as
members of CP9 for as long
as we can remember we've
trained to surpass the
limits of the human body
and vowed to hone those
skills into an instrument
of absolute justice
The results of that training are the
superhuman techniques known as the Six Powers.
So now I'm sure it's
abundantly clear to you why the
four of us are the
government's most elite agents.
And by the same token,
you must also realize how miserably
weak a band of pirates is in comparison.
Of course, the full extent of our
powers is strictly classified.
But rest assured, scum like
you would never make the cut.
Lucci, the ignition device
is about to detonate.
We should probably hurry.
But a chance like this one is quite rare.
Let me show you something interesting.
Devil Fruit powers!
Which one is it?
Lucci, what in the...?
Cat-cat fruit.
The leopard model
A human leopard He's
huge What's going on here
What in the hell are you